RG 002:014, Rejected Bills
Connecticut State Library
Rejected bills
1871-1911
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly
31.5 cubic feet
The Rejected bills described here cover the years 1871-1911. Rejected bills contain petitions, appointments, amendments, committee reports, drafts of legislation, and drafts of resolutions that did not pass.
RG002_014b
T003308
Scope and Content
Rejected bills begin in the year 1808 and continue until 1911. The rejected bills described here cover the years 1871-1911 and are closely related to the General Assembly Papers, 1821-2010. Starting in 1913, rejected bills can be found within. Rejected bills contain petitions, appointments, amendments, committee reports, drafts of legislation, and drafts of resolutions that did not pass.
Arrangement
Rejected bills are arranged by year.
Related Material
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
, Connecticut State Library.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly
Subjects:
Bills, legislative -- Connecticut; Connecticut -- Politics and government
Document Types:
Bills (legislative records); Petitions; Reports
Restrictions on Access
See the policy.
Custodial History
The General Assembly submitted these records to the Office of the Secretary of the State, which subsequently transferred them to the Connecticut State Library.
Container List
- Inventory, 1871-1911
  Boxes 45-64 are foldered.
  - 1871 (Box 45)
  - 1871-1872 (Box 46)
  - 1872-1873 (Box 47)
  - 1873-1874 (Box 48)
  - 1874-1875 (Box 49)
  - 1875 (Box 50)
  - 1876-1877 (Box 51)
  - 1877-1878 (Box 52)
  - 1879 (Box 53)
  - 1878-1879 (Box 54)
  - 1879-1880 (Box 55)
  - 1880-1881 (Box 56)
  - 1881 (Box 57)
  - 1881 (Box 58)
  - 1882 (Box 59)
  - 1882 (Box 60)
  - 1882-1883 (Box 61)
  - 1883 (Box 62)
  - 1883-1884 (Box 63)
  - 1883-1884 (Box 64)
  - 1883-1884 (Box 65)
  - 1884-1886 (Box 66)
  - 1886-1887 (Box 67)
  - 1887-1889 (Box 68)
  - 1889-1893 (Box 69)
  - 1893 (Box 70)
  - 1893-1895 (Box 71)
  - 1895-1897 (Box 72)
  - 1897-1899 (Box 73)
  - 1899 (Box 74)
  - 1901 (Box 75)
  - 1901 (Box 76)
  - 1901 (Box 77)
  - 1901-1903 (Box 78)
  - 1903 (Box 79)
  - 1903 (Box 80)
  - 1903-1905 (Box 81)
  - 1905 (Box 82)
  - 1905 (Box 83)
  - 1905-1907 (Box 84)
  - 1907 (Box 85)
  - 1907 (Box 86)
  - 1907 (Box 87)
  - 1907-1909 (Box 88)
  - 1909 (Box 89)
  - 1909 (Box 90)
  - 1909-1911 (Box 91)
  - 1911 (Box 92)
  - 1911 (Box 93)
  - 1911 (Box 94)
  - 1911 (Box 95)
  - 1911 (Box 96)